I can't believe he's gonna marry the girl
he cheated on me with.
(Leonard:)Isn't it kind of nice?
(Leonard:)He was with the wrong person.
Now he found the right person.
(Penny:)So I'm the wrong person?
Maybe you wanna be with Gretchen too.
(Bernadette:)They do look happy.
(Howard:)Yeah, maybe tonight.
(Howard:)But a year from now, he'll be crawling
under the sink looking for his Xbox.
(Howard:)Well, he will.
(Leonard:)Why don't we just forget about them
and enjoy our Valentine's Day?
(Penny:)Yes, absolutely.
Heh. Now they're doing that phony,
link-arm-drink thingy.
(Penny:)I totally taught him that.
- I thought we were letting it go.
- We were. It's just not fair, okay?
(Penny:)They're bad people.
(Penny:)Not supposed to end happy for them,
it's supposed to end happy for me.
(Leonard:)Um, it did end happy for you.
You're here with me.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah, I know.